(Sheldon:)All right,
I've taken the liberty
(Sheldon:)of drafting
these workflow charts
(Sheldon:)which outline our various duties
and the path we will follow
(Sheldon:)as we develop
our ground-breaking new app.
(Raj:)Hey, why am I in charge
of phone support?
(Raj:)Seems a bit racist.
(Sheldon:)A customer service
representative
(Sheldon:)with an Indian accent
will create the impression
(Sheldon:)we're a vast enterprise that
uses overseas call centers.
(Leonard:)Oh.
(Raj:)Very clever.
(Raj:)But still racist.
(Sheldon:)Duly noted, Steve
from Wichita.
(Howard:)Why am I listed as your
executive assistant?
Because the word "secretary"
has fallen into disrepute.
(Sheldon:)FYI, my mother's
birthday is coming up.
(Sheldon:)I'm going to need you
to pick up a present.
(Leonard:)Okay, we need
to stop for a minute.
(Sheldon:)Leonard, please,
we can talk during our break.
(Sheldon:)We have one coming up
at midnight.
(Sheldon:)We'll need snacks.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, you're not in charge.
(Leonard:)It's my idea.
I'm in charge.
(Sheldon:)Oh, of course you are.
(Sheldon:)Look at the organizational
chart.